[
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (1x + 10) + (10x + 1)?",
      "correctAnswer": "11x + 11",
      "options": [
        "11x + 11",
        "11x + 12",
        "12x + 11",
        "10x + 11"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (6x + 3) + (3x + 6)?",
      "correctAnswer": "9x + 9",
      "options": [
        "10x + 9",
        "8x + 9",
        "9x + 9",
        "9x + 10"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (6x + 9) + (9x + 6)?",
      "correctAnswer": "15x + 15",
      "options": [
        "16x + 15",
        "14x + 15",
        "15x + 15",
        "15x + 16"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (10x + 1) + (1x + 10)?",
      "correctAnswer": "11x + 11",
      "options": [
        "10x + 11",
        "11x + 11",
        "12x + 11",
        "11x + 12"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (5x + 10) + (10x + 5)?",
      "correctAnswer": "15x + 15",
      "options": [
        "15x + 16",
        "14x + 15",
        "15x + 15",
        "16x + 15"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (9x + 1) + (1x + 9)?",
      "correctAnswer": "10x + 10",
      "options": [
        "11x + 10",
        "10x + 11",
        "9x + 10",
        "10x + 10"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (3x + 1) + (1x + 3)?",
      "correctAnswer": "4x + 4",
      "options": [
        "4x + 4",
        "5x + 4",
        "3x + 4",
        "4x + 5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (7x + 4) + (4x + 7)?",
      "correctAnswer": "11x + 11",
      "options": [
        "11x + 12",
        "11x + 11",
        "10x + 11",
        "12x + 11"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (7x + 3) + (3x + 7)?",
      "correctAnswer": "10x + 10",
      "options": [
        "9x + 10",
        "10x + 10",
        "10x + 11",
        "11x + 10"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the simplified form of<br> (2x + 10) + (10x + 2)?",
      "correctAnswer": "12x + 12",
      "options": [
        "11x + 12",
        "12x + 12",
        "13x + 12",
        "12x + 13"
      ]
    }
]